♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call: ♪
- All right, let's go!
♪ Cambot ♪
- Pan left!
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Hi, girl!
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- What a cool guy!
♪ Croooow ♪
= He's a wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar twangs)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Okay, Gypsy, is it?
Okay, where are you from?
- Uh, right here
at the satellite.
- Uh-huh, and what do
you do for a living?
- You programmed me to do
some of the higher
functions of the ship.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, and who
does your hair, Gypsy?
I think that's great.
- Bite me.
- You live around here much?
I'm kidding of course.
- Hi everybody, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
A lot of you are probably
asking yourselves right now,
what kind of a weird
tripped out scene
is Joel into this week?
Well, it's--
Ow!
- Oh, sorry.
Get this, this week Joel
fancies himself a caricaturist.
Right now he's doing Gypsy.
For those of you who don't know,
a caricaturist is an artist
who makes anyone he draws
look like Jack Sue.
Ow, ow.
- The only problem
is, Gypsy's nude.
- Hey, you guys are
nude too, you know.
- What?
- Hey, he's right!
- Oh my god!
- Whoa!
- What do you think?
- Well...
(screaming)
(crashing)
- Well, at least I
can draw you, Cambot,
in the way I've
always wanted to.
Without a stitch on.
(instrumental theme music)
Well, what do you think?
- It's really not that good.
I look like Garrick Utley
with a cream pitcher
wedged in his skull.
- Well yours is pretty
good, isn't it Tom?
- Yeah, right.
Wouldn't pick up my worst
enemy's dog droppings
with this piece of crap.
Oh, but I'm sure
you'll get better.
Uh-oh, Dum-dum and
Stinkypants are calling there.
(chuckling)
- Dum-dum and Stinkypants,
where do they come
up with this stuff?
(chuckling)
Oh, I love that little red guy.
Oh look at me, I'm
a little red robot
and I can't move my arms.
- Frank.
- Huh?
- Why don't you ask them to do
their Invention Exchange, okay?
- Look, I love to laugh
and we're having fun,
but please, can we get to
the Invention Exchange?
(chuckling) Stinkypants.
- Well sirs, our Invention
Exchange this week
is based on those
beer can caddy hats
thatúshirtless obnoxious
guys wear at baseball games.
- Yeah, only ours are built for
whisper-thin, musky
bohemian types.
- Yeah. They're called
the Big Gulp Berets.
As you can see, they've
got caddies on the side
to hold your favorite
ice cold Evian or Volvic
or any other criminally
priced spring water.
- Now when you go see the
Bloody Unicorn Puppet Theater's
production of Marat Sade, you
can still have your hands free
to scribble poetry or
dab on patchouli oil.
- And at the dank uptown
cast party afterwards,
when the check comes, it frees
up your hands to discover...
- I must have left my
money in my other pants.
Could you spot me tonight?
What do you think, sirs?
- Very amusing, Joel,
but I don't cotton
to those long-haired
artsy types.
Now, you little scamps beg me
to do the Invention Exchange.
- (laughing) Okay, sirs.
Please do the
Invention Exchange.
- No.
Well, okay.
As a scientist, I'm constantly
working with materials
that threaten life
on a global scale,
and sometimes they spill.
Enter these polysorbent
biohazard clean-up pillows.
Once used only for
industry, we've brought them
into the home with
our new designer
biohaZard throw pillows.
Now Frank has prepared
a little one-act play
to explain their efficacy.
- Well, enough
Charles in Charge.
I'd better get to
work on that hardy new
strain of dysentery
I've been mutating.
Oh, no!
Not again!
Well, Dr. Forrester's decorator
biohazard clean-up pillows,
I'm saved!
Dr. Clayton
Forrester, I love you.
(clapping)
- Well Jimmy Smits,
your movie today
is roasted fresh from the
kitchens of Bert I. Gordon.
It's a fetid little
piece of tripe
featuring sword and
sorcery and Gary Lockwood
and an embarrassed
Basil Rathbone.
It's called The Magic Sword.
- Doctor, I think I sucked up
some of that hazardous stuff.
- Oh, don't be a baby, I've
taken gallons of that stuff
and it's only made me
stronger and taller.
- But I don't feel good.
- Oh what are you
gonna do now, cry, huh?
You gonna cry, baby, huh?
You gonna cry?
One, two, three, cry.
(alarms blaring)
- Oh, we got movie sign!
(all yelling)
(mechanical whirring)
- [Tom] Say, Bert I.
Gordon's gone color!
- [Joel] Can slice a tomato so
thin you can see through it.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Ah, I'll have Basil
Rathbone with pesto, please.
- [Joel] Give her a higher love.
- [Crow] Even then
she was really old.
- [Tom] Oh, you know,
I love Dean Martin
in those old Anne Helm movies.
- [Joel] Oh, it's Matt Helm.
Oh, Merritt Stone,
that's my birthstone.
- [Crow] Callahan,
it was Callahan.
Marlene Callahan,
she was the one.
- [Joel] Nick, Paul
and Jon Bon Tempi.
- [Crow] Is a woman who hangs
out with hags a hag hag?
- [Joel] No...
- [Tom] Makes ya
think, doesn't it?
Uh-oh, we're in
big trouble, guys.
- [Joel] We are in
really big trouble.
- [Tom] Yep, yep.
(Tom humming along with music)
- [Crow] Music made under
strict rabbinical supervision.
- [Tom] Dragon trainer,
they're kidding us, right?
- [Crow] This isn't a movie,
it's an employment program!
- [Tom] Isn't that what
they call you, girl?
Whadda they call you
up there in wardrobe?
- [Joel] They call
me Esther Krebs.
- [Tom] We are in deep,
deep trouble, guys.
And yes, you can be too thin.
- [All] Say...
Aaah!
- [Crow] Well...
- He left home hours ago.
- [Joel] Oh, that's so creative.
She has a little
cafe down there.
- What good is my sorcery
if I can't help my own boy?
Answer me, someone!
- [Crow] Roddy McDowell, no!
- He's not fooling me.
I know where he is.
He's at the magic pool again.
♪ A double pleasure's
waiting for you ♪
- He is in love.
- You think I don't know it?
I've tried to cure him of it.
Am I losing my skill
as a sorceress?
- [Tom] Among other things.
- No, no Sybil.
- [Crow] Oh, that's
calling the kettle black.
- To cure snakebite,
chillblains,
carbuncles, pinkeye, hangnails--
- [Joel] Hello, Mata.
- Yes, yes Sybil.
- Then why can't I rid the
boy of this, this fever?
- George is a man.
- [Tom] She hired two
brown-nosers to hang around.
- Human, yes, but hardly a man.
He's a mere boy of 20.
- In love.
- [Crow] You guys really bug me.
- George, already
a man, in love.
He ought to be at home
learning a good trade.
- [Joel] Like computer science,
refrigeration, gun repair.
- [Tom] Now is that
BJ or the Bear?
(Joel imitates vomiting)
- Pool of magic--
- [Crow] What?
- Obey my wish.
Bring her vision into my sight.
That's right, that's right.
- [Joel] Answer unclear,
ask again later.
- She's at the palace.
♪ It's the undersea kingdom,
for you and for me ♪
- Perhaps the throne room.
- [Joel] Calgon, take me away.
- [Crow] It's King Grady!
- [Joel] Oh, not another
Jane Fonda video.
(exotic music)
Imogene Coca, no!
- [Tom] Imogene Coca, yes.
Talk about your show of shows.
- [Crow] I hate
it when they hire
these strip-o-grams
for my birthday.
- Try the, try the sunken garden
in the palace by
the oriental pool.
- [Joel] Have breakfast
with me. (burbling)
- [Crow] Ah, somebody flushed.
- That's right, there she is.
- [Tom] Oh I get
it, he's got cable.
- There she is.
- [Crow] It's Fanny Fox.
- [Tom] It's a Maxfield
Parrish painting.
- [Joel] You're both
right, it's Fanny Fox
in a Maxfield Parrish painting.
Both jokes can work
together, let's watch on.
- [Tom] Hey mom, hey
mom, watch me mom,
watch me, watch this.
(burbling)
- [Crow] Gidget goes to
the Renaissance Festival.
- [Tom] That's
precise editing, huh?
- No, I'm just as
furious as ever.
- [Joel] I am furious yellow.
- You can do
whatever you please.
Fall in love, fall
out of it again.
A squire one day, a
stableboy the next.
- [Crow] I get the
point, all right!
Geez.
- I can't even speak to a man,
let alone have him look at me.
- That's the penalty
of being a princess.
- But even a princess
should be allowed romance.
- [Tom] Even cowgirls
get the blues.
- How will I ever meet him?
- [Girl] Who, my lady?
- One I could love.
- [Crow] Think that's
her natural color?
- [Joel] She has been
hitting the dye pot.
- But your gown.
- [Princess] I'll dress myself.
- Well then what will you do?
- Oh, what I always
do, sit here and dream.
- [Joel] Sit there and drink?
- [Woman] Princess Helene.
- [Tom] Your lights are on.
- Who are you?
- [Joel] Just came to
freak you out, baby.
- What do you want?
- [Joel] This doesn't
do anything for you?
Come on, I'm a ghost.
- Stay away!
- [Crow] Marcia Wallace!
- Don't you come any closer.
- No, Princess, I'm going
to take care of you.
- [Tom] She's stuck!
Bang her on the side
of the head there.
- [Crow] 2,000 flushes.
- Helene!
- [Tom] Delay?
- [Joel] It's Gary Lockwood.
- [Tom] It is.
- [Joel] Check this out.
Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
(giggling)
- [Tom] Good one.
- [Crow] 'Cause it's...
- [Tom] Mommy, mommy, mommy,
there was a scary
flashing thing, and it...
- Sybil, where are you!?
- You needn't shout, George.
- [Joel] Endora.
- I must leave here,
she's in danger.
- Who in the netherworld
are you talking about?
- Princess Helene.
I loved her from the
first moment I saw her.
(laughing)
- A reflection in the
water and you fall in love,
you silly child.
- [Crow] Last week, it
was a deck of cards.
- Let me see what
you're talking about.
Magic mirror, show me
what has upset my boy.
- [Crow] Adolescence,
puberty, raging hormones.
- The princess is
gone, your majesty.
She's not in her quarters,
not in the garden,
not by the pool, yet no one
saw her leave the palace.
- [Tom] Well, she
works late on Tuesdays.
- We have done that, my liege.
Until she is found, no
one will be permitted
in or out of the palace.
- [Joel] He's wearing
fighting alignment.
(trumpet music)
- [Crow] Can't you
just walk into the room
without a big to-do?
- [Tom] To-do!
- [Joel] He played
Sherlock Holmes, that one.
- Who is this?
- We found him skulking within
the eastern cluster, my liege.
- [Tom] I wasn't skulking,
I was hanging around.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Crow] Oh no, not a solo!
- Branton.
- Your most serene majesty,
you can call off the search.
The princess, your
daughter, is in my castle,
under lock and key.
- [Tom] Well, as long
as she's sa-- Hey!
- Lodac.
- The sorcerer.
- [Joel] No, the
pre-emergent tank mix,
of course it's the sorcerer!
- Lodac, you say my daughter
is at your castle, but why?
How have I hurt you?
Why have you done this thing?
- The answer is very simple.
Your father executed my
sister for witchcraft
when she was only 18 years old.
I have waited until your
daughter reached that age
so that my dragons could relish
the flesh of the princess.
- [Joel] Oh wow.
- I beseech you.
- Beseech nothing.
- [Tom] Ah, beseech this.
- [Branton] You'd have this
worm-eaten sorcerer frighten us.
- [King] Be careful, Branton.
- Not I.
Lodac--
- [Joel] You're a jerk.
- I shall find your
castle, free the princess
and see you destroyed.
- [Crow] All while
balancing an egg on a spoon.
- Finding my castle
is no great task.
- [Tom] Hey, MC Light
wants her necklace back.
- You simply follow the
yellow star up north.
The trick is how
to get there alive.
- I shall.
- I'm afraid not.
(instrumental theme music)
(thunder rumbles)
- [Tom] Uh, Houston, we
have lift-off, roger.
- That I shall be in
this castle of mine.
- [Crow] He's got
a reverb pedal.
- Who dares to
dart through this.
(thunder rumbles)
Let no man face my seven curses
and reach the dragon's lair.
- [Joel] You ain't woman
enough to take my man.
- Your curses won't stop me.
- [Tom] Femme for
all seasons here.
- The Princess Helene will make
a delicate dish for my dragon.
- [Crow] I'm serving her
over rice with fava beans.
(imitating Hannibal Lecter)
- And now, if you'll excuse me.
- [Tom] Uh, was that
seven days starting now,
or is it seven days start--
- [Crow] Aaah-aaah-aaah.
Nevermore, nevermore!
- [Tom] Well, suppose that
could have gone better.
- Sir Branton, my
daughter will die.
- No, Sire, for I
will rescue her.
- You'll risk the seven curses?
- [Crow] (chuckling) I
love that Carlin bit.
- The man who saves Helene
will have her hand in marriage
and half my kingdom.
- [Joel] Check it out, she
looks like Ronald McDonald.
- [Crow] No one's
supposed to know.
- No, no, it is I who
must save the princess,
not Sir Branton!
(Tom repeating mockingly)
- Do you think I'd let
you face Lodac's sorcery?
- [Joel] You don't have
your learner's permit.
- 300 years ago my
father and brother
were devoured by Lodac's dragon.
- [Crow] Not this story again.
- They were great sorcerers
in their own right.
- [Tom] I remember it
like it was 200 years ago.
- I am no match for
Lodac, I confess it.
- [Joel] Okay, okay!
- But Sybil--
- [Tom] Please, I
gesticulate you!
- Stay right here at
home where you are safe.
- [Joel] You're grounded.
- You can have anything you
want, but you're staying here.
- All I want is my freedom so
I can save the girl I love!
- [Tom] All I want is
what's coming to me!
- But you wouldn't understand
that, not being mortal!
- [Crow] Oh, that hurt.
- I've tried to do my best.
- Oh, I know you have, Sybil.
- [Sybil] Can't
you call me Mother?
- [Joel] Oh, is it Mother today?
- Sorry, Mother.
- You were only a week old
when your royal parents
died from the plague.
- [Tom] Those were
happier times.
- I found you, reared
you as my own son.
- [Crow] Must have the
answers written on his hand.
- And I'd do anything for you,
but I can't stay here
with you anymore.
- [Joel] It's weird!
- I'm not a child, I'm
20 and I love Helene.
- Talk to me of love
when you're 420.
- When you're human,
20 is old enough
to feel love and misery.
And give me my freedom.
- [Joel] Okay, but
it's not wrapped.
- You're being very
difficult tonight.
Oh well, boys will be boys.
- [Crow] In the hood.
- We'll have to cheer you up.
Watch Mother now.
(Crow imitates cracking)
- [Joel] I'm gonna have
a big bowl of Quisp.
- [Crow] Get that
lady a saucer of milk.
(Tom growls)
- Not that trick again.
- [Crow] Again?
Does he have a cotton
panel in those briefs?
- George.
- [Tom] Don't ya know me?
- I've never seen
you like this before.
Look, if you'll cheer up, forget
about that girl and Lodac,
I'll let you see the
presents I've chosen for you
when you're 21.
- [Joel] A new codpiece?
- What sort of presents, Mother?
- Come along.
♪ It's Alexander's
ragtime band ♪
- I'll show you.
- [Tom] Packed with peanuts,
Estelle really satisfies.
- [Crow] Oh, yes.
- [Tom] Crow.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] Why do you seek
the living among the dead?
- [Tom] Carol Merrill,
what's behind that curtain?
It's a new horse!
(imitating cheering)
- You like him?
- [Joel] Geez, any
kid would, he's swell!
- He's magnificent.
- [Sybil] He's yours when
you're 21, his name is Beyard.
He's no ordinary animal.
- [Crow] He's your father.
- [Sybil] This is the fastest
horse in all the world.
♪ I am Mister Edgar Winter ♪
- [Tom] And it can all be
yours if the price is right.
- [Joel] Take the door!
- [Crow] Go for the curtain!
- [Tom] Curtain, curtain!
Oh.
(giggling)
- [Joel] A candy striper's
outfit, thanks Mom!
- See this?
You'll wear it when
you ride the stallion.
- [Crow] Used to
be your sister's.
- Does this armor
possess magic too?
- No weapon can pierce it.
- [Tom] 'Cept a butter knife.
- And this is
Ascalon, the blade.
None like it since
the world began,
it defies all swords--
- [Joel] It's a Ginsu 2000.
- So there, all
yours when you're 21.
- [Tom] If the price is right.
- I'll let you go after Lodac
for my revenge as
well as your own.
- With the help of their magic,
I could save the princess now.
- No, you're not old enough.
You wouldn't know
how to use them.
- [Joel] No, don't touch it.
Don't even look at it.
- Just to get the feeling.
Just for a while.
(chuckling)
- Very well.
- Feels like a part
of my own body.
- [Crow] So it's like your arm?
- I feel stronger.
- [Tom] More
confident, dry, secure.
- It pleases me to show
you something else tonight.
- [Joel] Boss, it's
a Hank Aaron model.
- Who are they?
- [Crow] The Village People!
- [Sybil] The six most
valiant knights in the world.
- [Joel] That's him,
Officer, third from the left.
- [George] That's
real black magic.
- I wish I could
take the credit.
I've never been as good as
that, no, it was my brother.
- [Tom] Geez Mom, all
this stuff was in my room
and I never noticed it before!
- Just great.
- [Joel] Now I can be the prep
cook I always wanted to be~
(sword clanging)
- [Tom] Oh now I've
done it, sorry Mom.
- Did the sword do that?
- [Crow] Sure did, Jethro.
- One touch of the blade
and it opens and shuts
floors, doors, walls
and portcullises.
- [Joel] And its snapples caps
off jugs, bottles and jars.
- Shuts them too, you say.
- [Tom] What the hell.
- What's down there?
- [Tom] China.
- I haven't been down
there in centuries.
It used to be my brother's
safe deposit box storeroom.
Spells, enchantments,
magic rituals and the like.
Want to see?
- [Joel] Old magazines and
my high school yearbook.
- Is there any other way out
if the crack were closed again?
- [Crow] Well, there's
the kitchen door.
- A cousin of mine took 80
years to work up a spell
that blew the roof off, but...
- [Tom] She's got more
stories about her relatives
than Gabe Kaplan.
- I'm not afraid.
You go first, Mother.
- [Tom] Age before
beauty, I guess.
Whoa, I didn't wanna see that.
♪ One singular sensation ♪
- [Tom] Hey.
(sword clanging)
- [Joel] Psych!
- [Sybil] George!
- [Joel] My toe!
- [Sybil] George, what have
you done? George, let me out.
- Goodbye, Mother.
- [Sybil] George!
George, let me out this instant.
You can't leave me here, I
told you about my cousin!
- I'll come back and let you out
after I've rescued
the princess Helene.
- [Tom] But I'll
be hungry by then.
- With the magic armor,
magic sword, magic steed.
- [Crow] And my
refrigeration certificate
from Pine City Vo-Tech.
- [Sybil] You don't know Lodac.
George, George, let me out!
- [Joel] (scoffing) Taffeta.
- [Tom] Let's go.
- [Joel] Hey, Basil Rathbone,
that gives me an idea.
Remember those doggie
costumes we had?
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
(bots whining and barking)
You know, you get out of your
dog what you put into it.
- [Magic Voice] Top
trainer, Joel Robinson.
- And I only put in the
best, Basil Rathbones.
Okay, Crow, okay.
Okay boy, wait for
it, wait for it..
Good!
(laughing)
You know, a top-trained
dog like this one
is a lot like any of us people.
You know, we all need
affection, occasional grooming
and lots and lots of snacks.
And dogs just go nuts for the
rich taste of Basil Rathbones.
One Rathbone a day will
clean doggie's teeth
and freshen doggie breath.
- And they're packed
with bits of Nigel Bruce,
- Hey, these are too
good to be good for you!
- Okay Tom Servo, sit, sit.
Good doggie.
(laughing) Basil Rathbones.
- And pesto-flavored
Basil Rathbones,
for the pretentious dog.
- [Magic Voice] Now in
rice and stick flavor,
- It's alimentary,
my dear Robinson
, to love Basil Rathbones.
- Have my doggies been good
on the Satellite of Love?
Oh, they are such
good, good doggies.
Do the doggies want
to go out and...
(instrumental theme music)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] We bring you
tennis balls, your majesty.
- [Tom] Woof.
Got fur in my mouth.
Your majesty,
these knights and I
have come to serve you
in your hour of need.
- That is very kind.
- [Tom] But we're
not hiring right now.
- I am Sir George, a
knight by virtue of
400 years of noble lineage.
- [Crow] And a degree from
Cardinal Stritch College.
- These are my comrades in arms.
Sir Dennis of France.
- Your majesty--
- [Joel] He's gonna have
really bad hat hair.
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- [George] Sir
Ulrich of Germany.
- Mein Keiser, we come to serve.
- [Joel] The voice
of Paul Frees.
- [George] Sir Anthony of Italy.
- [Tom] Yo, Tony!
- [Joel] Harry Shearer.
- [George] Sir Pedro of Spain.
- [Crow] He's got an
observatory on his head.
- [George] Sir
James of Scotland.
- Our hearts grieve for you
in your sorrow, your majesty.
- [George] And last--
- [Joel] Terry, the
sensitive knight.
- We pledge our
lives to your service
and to the princess
Helene until she's safe.
- [Crow] What, is he the
knight from the Bronx?
- Speaking for the king, we
are grateful for your offer.
I am sure that you can be
of immeasurable service
to his majesty while I'm away.
- [Tom] We'll keep
your resumes on file.
- Oh, you know who I am.
Have we met?
- [Crow] That's an old line.
- In the field?
- Not in the field.
And I also know you wish to
marry the princess Helene.
- Quite true.
You're all welcome to stay
and dance at my wedding.
- [Tom] Yeah, me and what army?
Oh.
- Many thanks,
but I prefer to dance at my own.
- [Crow] Uh, we're getting
into a weird area here.
- Don't try to solve them until
we've rescued the
princess Helene.
- We?
- [Joel] What do you
mean we, Kemosabe?
- Monsieur, try to understand.
We are all sworn to save
Sir George's beautiful lady.
- [Tom] I think what our
bright young French friend
is trying to say is...
- What does the Frenchman mean?
- Only that I love her
and I intend to marry her.
- [Tom] Oh okay--
Hey!
- Do you know the perils
of the dark journey?
- We do, Sir Branton.
If you don't share
our enthusiasm,
we shall be happy to
go on without you.
- [Joel] Ha ha ha huh?
- Your majesty, have I
your permission to give
this stripling a lesson
in the use of arms?
- [Crow] Permission to
cut him ib half, sir!
- I shall not draw.
- [Tom] I shall paint.
- Except on behalf
of Princess Helene.
- A coward.
Draw.
(sword clanging)
- [Joel] Jerk, you
broke my sword!
(crowd murmuring)
- Enough, that's enough!
Sir Branton, I
like these knights.
- [Crow] You violated ape law.
- You and seven good swords.
- Seven swords.
- [Tom] For seven brothers.
- Seven curses.
- When do we start, Sir Branton?
- Now.
- [Crow] On your
mark, get set, go!
- [Joel] Hi-keeba.
(frustrated grumbling)
- [Tom] And a double hi-keeba.
I just raised him one.
♪ Knights in white satin ♪
- [Tom] Come on, you
ragtag bunch of misfits.
- [Crow] Whew, glad I don't
jave to mow that lawn.
- [Tom] Looks like
a golf course.
- [Joel] Tonight on Mime Court.
- [Crow] If you're really bad,
they throw you in
the imaginary box.
- [Joel] Petticoat Dungeon.
- I'm Helene.
- We know, we heard you were
brought in this morning.
I'm Princess Laura, and
this is my sister Grace.
This is our seventh day.
- [Crow] Let's
form a girl group.
- Our last day, unless...
- Surely you don't believe
that about the dragon.
- There were others
here when we arrived,
but they're gone now.
- [Tom] Georgette, everybody.
- Then your father will
do something to save you.
Why, his army is probably
approaching the castle
this very minute.
- [Joel] Don't kid
yourself, sister.
We've been here for seven years.
- You'll be on your
way home by morning.
(roaring)
- [Crow] Uh, that's my dad.
- The two sisters.
♪ There were never
such devoted sisters ♪
- [Crow] Eraserhead.
- [Joel] Literally.
- Are we to go home now,
has Father arranged
for our release?
- You're not going home.
- [Crow] You're
going to Disneyland.
- Surely you've spoken to him?
- I've had three long,
dull sessions with him
but nothing could persuade him
to give up what I asked for.
- I don't believe you,
he'd pay you anything!
- Nothing.
Instead, he sent
an entire company
of his bravest knights
on the dark journey.
The poor lads never even
reached the third curse.
Take them away.
- [Joel] They bore me.
(princesses screaming)
- [Crow] Can I take their
Snoopy poster down now?
- This just can't be happening.
There just couldn't be anybody
as cruel and evil as you.
- [Tom] No, I won't hear it!
There's a man in Eastbourne.
- You think this
is the first time
that a princess has
been fed to a dragon?
At least around here it
happens only once a week.
- Unless you get what you want.
What ransom are
you asking for me?
- I'm sorry, but you happen
to be a particular case.
I'm not asking any
ransom for you at all.
- Then why did
you bring me here?
- My little pet will be hungry
again in six days' time.
(roaring)
- [Crow] Uh, five days' time.
- No, no please.
No, please.
- [Joel] Is she soup yet?
- [Tom] Mmm, mmm, dead.
- The wind carries well.
Don't turn your head away,
you'll miss all the fun.
You see?
- [Crow] Ah, he does light cues.
- It happens very quickly.
Now my little pet can sleep.
- It's horrible.
- [Joel] Oh bite me, it's fun.
- But it won't happen to me.
Their father sent a company.
Well mine will send an army!
- [Tom] My Westley
will come for me.
- I hate to disillusion you.
Actually, for a while,
your father seemed content
to let just one knight
undertake your rescue.
Oh, don't blame your father.
The knight talked him into it.
- And who is this
very brave knight?
- I'm sure you know him.
- [Joel] Murray.
- Sir Branton.
- [Joel] Sir Frampton?
- [Tom] Oh, he's a freshman.
- You don't like Sir Branton?
Oh, come now.
A damsel in distress can't
afford to pick and choose.
Anyway, don't worry.
Neither he nor his companions
will ever get here.
- Companions, I thought you
said Sir Branton was alone.
- He would have been, but
some foolhardy young man
named George insisted
on coming with him.
- George?
- [Lodac] Of course,
you don't know him.
- [Joel] You don't
know him, he's new.
- Where is he?
- Would you care to see him?
- [Crow] Feel him, touch him?
- Certainly, I'll show
you the young fool.
- [Tom] It's pay-per-view,
we can only watch it
for two minutes
before they charge us.
- Which one is George?
- The youngest.
He's in the lead,
riding with Sir Branton.
- [Joel] Boy, that place
could use some yardwork.
- [Tom] Looks like
Cypress Gardens, Florida.
- Those who are wise
will turn back now.
- [Tom] Okay, see ya.
- Bye, thanks.
- [Crow] Hah, they're
riding carousel horses
like Marry Poppins.
(instrumental theme music)
- [Tom] Look, that
guy hit a bug.
- [Crow] Oh, we're
back, nothing there.
- [Joel] It's a K.O.A.
- [Tom] You guys cower
over here, I'll go look.
- [Crow] Oh, let
me see this thing.
- [Tom] Huh?
(growling)
- [Joel] Teddy Ruxpin, no!
- [Tom] Kinda looks
like Gino Vannelli.
(growling)
- [Tom] Ouch.
- [Crow] Sanctuary, sanctuary!
- [Tom] Sanctuary
much. (chuckling)
Think that hurts,
look at this perm!
- [Joel] It's Ron Perlman.
- [Crow] Ah shoot,
this is real fur!
You know how hard it
is to get blood out?
(growling)
- [Tom] It's a salted nut log.
Captain's log. (chuckling)
- [Joel] That's his
only move, essentially.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] Pretty much.
- [Crow] All right,
anyone know what that is?
- Keep back always, he's mine.
- [Tom] He's yours?
Then tell him to stop
throwing stuff at us!
- [Joel] We talked about it
and we'd really appreciate it
if you'd stop throwing things.
- [Tom] Yeah, it's over
by the Seven-Eleven
and you take a left,
okay, by the freeway.
- [Crow] Heh-heh, it's
a troll in the hay!
- [Tom] D'oh!
- [Joel] Literally.
- [Tom] Kinda looks like
Barry Gibb, doesn't he?
- [Joel] Have some pumpernickel
bread with me, friend, here.
- [Crow] Stop, that's
no way to kill roaches.
- [Tom] Now he's
throwing beefsteak rye.
Sure is hearty.
- [Joel] Ah, I gotta learn
to lead that little guy.
♪ Round round, get around,
I get around yeah ♪
- [Crow] Goofy, isn't it?
- That horse is swift.
- [Tom] It's a pilot,
so it's an hour long.
- No, no, no, no.
Just a stupid thought
that crossed my mind.
- [Tom] I thought maybe you
and I could, oh never mind.
- My ogre will kill them both.
- [Crow] His odor?
- Are you quite sure?
- [Tom] He needs Ogre
Eaters. (laughing)
- [Joel] I am not an animal.
- [Crow] Look out,
he's gonna launch!
- [Tom] He's kinda got Conway
Twitty hair doesn't he?
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- [Crow] Watch this,
kinda pathetic.
- [Joel] Ga-nish!
- [Tom] Ga-nish?
- [Crow] Ya got me. (groaning)
- [Tom] Chest Hair
Club, for men.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm gonna
make him into a fort!
(bots cheering)
- He's won!
He beat you at your own game.
- So he did.
- [Tom] Now where's
my ten bucks?
- He'll save me, I know he will.
- Not a chance.
No one has ever survived
the seven curses of Lodac.
That was only the first.
- [Joel] Now it's six curses!
- [Crow] Shut up, shut up!
- [Tom] He's evil, but he
should spat more, you know?
- [Joel] They buried him?
- And still not a sign of our
gallant commander, Sir Branton.
- [Crow] You make me
sick, you stupid pig.
- Not to pay respect
when poor Ulrich
and Pedro are laid to rest.
- But is the man a
coward, not to have
lifted his sword
against that monster?
- Branton's no coward.
- [Crow] They're praying
over the monster's butt.
- We missed you at the
burial, Sir Branton.
- [Joel] Don't say hi.
- My regrets, gentlemen,
are as deep as your own,
but since every minute
counts, I thought it wiser
for me to ride ahead
and reconnoiter.
(Tom imitates chicken clucking)
- Mount your horses, gentlemen.
- [Crow] We're not that lonely!
- And come see for yourselves.
- [Joel] Yeah, let's
get outta here.
The mists of Avalon.
♪ Avalon ♪
- [Tom] This is a hair follicle
magnifiedúover a million times.
- [Joel] You know,
I was just thinking
this is really pretty
good for a Bert I...
- [Crow] What!?
- [Tom] Well yeah,
for Bert I. Gordon.
- [Crow] Well...
♪ I get misty ♪
♪ Smoke gets in your eyes ♪
♪ Smoke on the ♪
- [Crow] Oh, for
cryin' out loud!
(laughing)
♪ On top of Old Smokey ♪
- [Crow] Okay.
- [Joel] Hollywood Hot Tubs Two.
- [Tom] Really makes
ya think, don't it?
- [Joel] Nope.
(water bubbling)
- [Tom] Just what I mean,
I was trying to think of
something to say, I mean we're
supposed to be on a quest.
We're supposed to
be best friends,
we haven't even talked yet.
- [Joel] We've talked.
- [Tom] No, no, I
mean really talked.
All I know about you
is that you're French.
France is a big country and all.
- [Joel] Not really.
- [Crow] Are we in
the Renaissance?
- [Joel] No, no, we're
in the early Middle Ages.
- [Crow] How do you know?
- [Joel] Well, take
the distinction
between the slave
and the free man.
- [Crow] What about it?
- [Joel] Well, it's weakening.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] You know, even if
we were in the Renaissance,
how would we know we
were in the Renaissance?
- [Knight] Would you
look at that, George?
- [Crow] Wow.
It's a virtual bloodbath.
- [Joel] Literally.
- [Tom] This may be a quest,
but it's also kind
of fun isn't it?
- This would be an unsavory
region, Sir Branton.
- [Crow] So fair and foul
a day I have not seen.
- Why, it isn't a
road we're on at all.
The fog's getting thicker.
Where's Dennis?
- [Joel] At Mr. Wilson's?
- Where's James and Anthony?
James, Dennis!
Anthony!
- [Tom] I say it's a bit foggy!
- Well then keep
with us, keep close!
- [Crow] And keep
reaching for the stars~
- [Knight] Where's Anthony?
Anthony!
- [Joel] It's Prince
spaghetti day!
- [Knight] Anthony!
Anthony!
- [Tom] Nothing, I'm
just playing over here!
- [Joel] This is a hair
follicle after being blow-dried.
- [Knight] Anthony!
- [Crow] Look,
Anthony's gone, okay?
(Joel and Tom imitating
jungle animals)
- [Knight] Anthony!
- [Joel] Zerbe!
- [Knight] Which way are you?
- Here!
- [Crow] I'm over here
in the hydrangea bush!
- [Tom] Strider, Boromir!
- [Joel] It's Dean Jones
in The Love Knight, ha ha.
(screaming)
- Find him!
- Anthony, where are you?
- [Crow] Now I am
over here drowning!
- Where are you?
- [Anthony] I'm here!
- [Tom] Uh, I need specifics.
Exactly what does here mean?
- I'm being pulled under.
- Give me your hand.
(all applauding)
- [Joel] Yay.
- Give me your hand.
- [Joel] Okay!
(all applauding)
You just ate, get out
of there, quit clowning.
- [Crow] My beard's coming off.
How you two doing over
here, everything okay?
Ah, carry on.
- [Joel] Hmm, his torso's gone,
he's been eaten by piranha!
- [Tom] Have a nice
trip, see you next fall.
- [Crow] I don't go for
that kinda stuff, hey!
- [Joel] That poor bastard
never knew what hit him.
(instrumental theme music)
Uh, huzzah everybody, I am
noble and happy King Joel
and we're about to present
our whimsical and charming
pageant based on life in
the middle ages, Crow?
- That's Sir Crow.
- Right, Sir Crow of Robot.
- Why yes, Sir Crow of
Robot, defender of the realm,
guardian of the flame,
purveyor of fine toiletries
to her majesty's
court since 1753.
A noble, wandering,
virtuous knight.
Yep, in days of old
when knights were bold
and toilets needed--
- Thst's good, that's
really good, Crow.
- But I'm not finished.
- Oh, I think you are.
Ah, but soft, behold
the fair maiden.
- Aye, but she's
a toothsome wench.
- Speak thee, Gypsy.
What love could press
thee from mine side?
Speak, fair Gypsy, what love
could press thee from mine side?
- Uh, oh.
My only love sprung from my...
- Only hate!
- Only hate, too early seen
unknown and known too late.
Prodigious birth of love...
- It is to me.
- It is to me, that I
must love mine enemy.
- Bummer.
Well, the great thing
about Gypsy's hat here
is that this comes out and
she can double as a unicorn,
like that, it's kinda neat.
Okay, places everybody, it's
time for my big coronation.
Where's Tom?
- Good my lord,
at your feet sire.
- Uh, Tom, you'd better
get your costume on,
we're ready for the big pageant.
- Uh, this is my costume.
- Oh you have got to
be kidding me, Servo.
- No really, I'm a serf.
- A what?
- You know, an agrarian
serf, indentured servant,
sort of a low-level
non-cameral prole.
- Like a poor person?
- Well, you know, poverty
was a relative state
to me and my kind in
the Middle Ages, Cypsy.
You see, having no chance
to acquire property
except through
indentured servitude
and due to the plague,
the overburdened farmland
and the Germsn countryside
before the Hapsburg and...
- Listen Tom, you're taking
this way too seriously, okay?
Listen, Crow is just a
knight, Gypsy is just
a lady in waiting who
doubles as a unicorn,
and I'm a noble,
good-hearted and happy king.
(laughing)
- Sure, Mad Ludwig, I could
count the good-hearted kings of
even the high Middle Ages on
my inarticulate little finger.
You know many despotic
trumped-up monarchs there were
born into madness due
to massive inbreeding
to the point that schizophrenia
was a sign of nobility.
- What about ladies in waiting?
- Well, you're gonna have
to wait a long time, girl.
Courtly love was a veritable
spawning ground for
social diseases.
You're better off as a unicorn
and they don't even exist!
- Oh, is the great Servo
going to give us
a morality lesson?
- Yeah, stick around,
Sir Cheddar Clownsalot,
you may learn something.
Besides, you know most knights
were illiterate, belching
maniacal landed gentry
who vainly attempted
to assert their masculinity
by going on errant raids
of undefended villages
and by impaling each other
in brutal tournaments.
- You wanna kill
him or should I?
- Give him the bare
bodkin, my buddy.
- Avant, and quit
my sight, dickweed!
(yelling)
Hey, King Joel, serf's up!
- All right!
- Watch out for movie sign!
(alarms blaring)
- Oh, we got movie
sign, let's go!
(mechanical whirring)
- [Tom] I was just
trying to make a point,
you didn't have to impale me!
- [Crow] Sorry.
- [Tom] Oh, it's
the rinse cycle.
- Or you'll die too!
- [Joel] They
deep-fried his sword!
It's got a crispy coating.
A crunchy crispy coating.
- [Tom] Tender on the inside.
Down for the third time.
- [Crow] Oh, it really
cleared up his skin.
- [Tom] Hey, wanna listen
to some Dead? (laughing)
- [Joel] Deep heating.
- [Crow] Must get to
crappy special effect.
- [Joel] I'm tired of
the whole sordid affair!
- [Tom] Sword-ed? (chuckling)
- [Joel] Yeah, kind of a spin.
- [Tom] Going up, Sir George?
- [Crow] Uh, I'm okay!
- Haver you seen those amis?
- Where's Anthony?
- Where's George?
- [Tom] Where's Waldo?
- [Crow] Where's papa?
- They are lost for good.
- Not George, look!
- [Joel] I found a
horse, can I keep him?
- Anthony has joined
Pedro and Ulrich.
- Forward, gentlemen.
- [Crow] Try to
stay on the path.
- [Tom] We're well into the
third game of the tournament.
Ah, I see Snuggles the chimp
has opted for the
French defense.
And Telly Savalas
and Telly Savalas
are pondering their move.
Ah, the Persian, of course.
(rumbling)
- [Joel] Mom's home!
- [Tom] Tonight on
Tales from Lucy's Crypt.
- [Crow] Aah, Ricky,
welcome ro the crypt.
I've been lurking for you.
- [Joel] Ooh, what
did I do last night?
- [Crow] Glad she's back.
Tonight, on a very
special My Weird Body.
- [Tom] A Henry Moore sculpture.
- [Joel] We'll be back
to My Wacky Witch.
(sighing)
- [Tom] Bring Mommy
a beer, come on.
- [Joel] Mommy
needs her medicine.
- [Crow] Ah, the strange
loves of Martha Ivers.
- [Tom] A delicious
shake for breakfast,
another for lunch and a
strange elixer for dinner.
- [Joel] Ah, dry ice
does it every time.
- My, what a job
getting out of there.
- [Tom] What a drag
it is getting old.
- Wait til I get
my hands on him.
- George?
- After all I've
done for that boy.
To trick me, put
me in his power,
me, his own foster mother!
- [Crow] Dual overhead
Sinead O'Connors.
- Lodac.
- [Tom] Geez, I
hired these guys?
- His life is in danger.
- You're tired.
- Jinx.
- Tired.
- Rest, rest.
- Jinx, j-jinx.
- I'll never rest again
until I know he's safe.
Oh my boy, what have you done?
Mirror of magic, bring
me a vision of my boy.
- [Tom] Oh, everybody's
got one of those.
I thought they were special.
- You and I have a good reason
to continue the dark journey.
Both of us in love
with the same girl.
Each of us hopes to rescue her.
- [Joel] Oh curses, a
Bert I. Gordon film.
- As your commander,
I honestly advise you
to turn back now while
there is still time.
- [Crow] Uh, you're in the fire.
(blowing)
- George, we should turn
heel and ride back to safety
leaving you and Sir Branton?
- [Tom] Well said,
take a breath.
- That makes good sense.
- Are your wits addled?
- Lodac's curses
have already claimed
Ulrich, Pedro and Anthony.
- As long as there's
one of us left alive,
there's hope that the
princess can be saved.
- [Crow] You know, he almost
got that Irish accent.
- I couldn't blame
you for leaving.
- Between the curses of Lodac
and Branton's treachery,
you'll be needin' us.
- You Irish dog, what do
you mean by such insolence?
- Dog am I, you
two-faced hypocrite!
- [Joel] And the bench is clear!
- I demand an explanation.
- You shall have one.
- [Tom] You're out of order!
- My knights believe you prefer
to continue the journey alone,
so you can get rid of him.
- What nonsense.
- You can't deny that from the
first, you refused our help.
- [Joel] Ya got me.
- Well of course I didn't
want you coming along.
After all, what man wants to
join forces with his rival?
But once we had begun
the dark journey,
I accepted you completely.
- [Crow] I love you
unconditionally.
- Yet you would have
us leave Sir George.
- What suspicious minds.
♪ We can't go on together ♪
- Lodac's curses
are killing us off
one by one, curse by curse.
- Be that as it may,
I stay with George.
- [Joel] Bailey.
- We'd still be statues
staring at the blasted wall
if George hadn't turned
us into men again.
- [Tom] Great, Darryl speaks up.
- And what good is
it being a man again
if you can't help
win the fair Helene?
- Thank you, Pat.
- [Crow] But I'll
take it from here.
- All of you.
There's your answer.
- [Tom] Uh, what
was the question?
- I have to admire your courage.
- [Joel] Though not your smock.
- Goodnight.
- [Crow] I gotta go lift.
- His tongue is like the
honey from a clover patch.
I do not believe a
word the man says.
- - If his game proves to
be treachery, it will be
Sir Branton who does not
return from this journey.
This I swear.
- [Joel] The mighty
birch, king of all trees.
Ask for it by name.
- [Crow] Best not to do
your treachery at noon.
(Tom yawning)
- [Tom] Oh, I dreamed
I saw a buffalo shot.
- [Crow] Hey, where
are ya taking me?
I don't wanna go!
I object, get off me.
- [Joel] Somebody
opened the garage door.
- [Tom] Ah, geez.
I gotta go hit my shift
at the Happy Chef.
♪ At the Copa, Copaca ♪
- [Joel] Oh, here it is.
- [Tom] Hey, it's Willa
Cather's birthplace.
- [Crow] Where'd that
door go, oh there it is.
- [Joel] Come out, come
out, wherever you are.
- [Lodac] Ah, Branton.
- [Joel] Are you decent?
- Right here.
- Well, I see you're
in a good mood.
(Joel imitates cat hissing)
- On the contrary.
I'm in a savage mood.
(Tom growls)
I can't stand incompetence.
You were to come here
alone on this phony rescue.
- [Crow] Funky rescue.
- Talk about incompetence.
In three days, you've
only managed to destroy
three of these interfering fools
with all your magic powers.
- Not all my magic
powers, Branton.
- [Joel] Uh, most of them.
- Give me my ring,
and I'll dispose of
these men in quick order.
- [Crow] Not til I
get my bicycle back.
- What use is the ring to you?
No mortal can command its magic.
- You'll get your ring back
when I get the princess.
That was our bargain.
- Don't you trust me?
- [Joel] Don't you trust me?
- You're insolent!
- [Tom] No one in
my organization
has ever talked to me that way.
- And take the ring!
- Go ahead.
- Give me my ring, now.
Now!
- [Crow] You gonna cry, crybaby?
Cry, you're gonna cry.
- But once you have it back,
what's to save me
from your curses?
- [Tom] You're wonderful.
- [Joel] Well, I've prepared
a small demonstration.
- Why would I want to hurt you?
- [Crow] 'Cause you're a jerk!
- Why wouldn't you?
You're only helping me now
because you want to
get back this ring,
which you so stupidly lost.
- [Joel] Sounds like
a Noel Coward play.
- I'll keep my word.
I'll give it back in five
days' time, when these curses
are behind me and I've
claimed the princess.
- [Tom] Please, keep
the smock as our gift.
- You're a tough
trader, Branton.
- We both know what we want,
and we're both going to get it
so long as you dispose
of these knights,
especially Sir George.
- [Joel] You Can Negotiate
Anything, by Basil Rathbone.
- Twice he's squirmed
out of your trap
and he could do it again.
- Oh, stop that.
You're worse than an old woman.
- [Crow] Yeah, he should know.
- If George and his knights
are not dead by week's end...
- They'll die long before that.
- [Joel] Look, you can see the
string that works his mouth.
- Worse than anything
I've conjured up yet.
One of them's coming
here now, to his death.
- [Tom] Stop following me!
- Well.
- [Crow] Hello, Uhura.
- The gallant Frenchman.
- [Joel] You don't
see many of those.
(Crow singing in French)
- He's seen my horse.
- It's all right.
- [Crow] And he is a Frenchman.
- Don't lose your head.
Let him come in here,
we'll be ready for him.
- [Tom] So, why does the
most evil man in the world
live in a Stuckey's?
- [Joel] He likes
the pecan pralines?
- [Crow] It's the
broasted chicken.
- [Tom] Nut log.
(girl singing Frere Jacques)
(All singing along)
(speaking French)
- [Tom] What would
you do, folks?
- Mignonette.
(grunting)
- [Joel] Sleeping in
armor is hard on a body.
- [Crow] Ah, just let it ring.
- [Tom] Huh, armor with memory.
- [Joel] You taste
like Charles Boyer.
- [Tom] So is this
French kissing?
(laughing)
(speaking French)
- [Crow] Yes, and
those Americans,
they can't appreciate
a good meal.
(speaking French)
- [Joel] Oh Tish,
you spoke French!
- Mademoiselle--
- uh-uh, uh-uh, no.
- [Tom] Come come, we've been
dating for almost two minutes.
(speaking French)
- [Crow] He's Pepe LePew!
- [Joel] Cat people.
- [Tom] Boy, he really had the
beer goggles on, didn't he?
- [Crow] Hey all
right everybody,
Frenchie's gettin' some!
(Tom cheering)
- [Joel] Oh man, I know
he's French, but her?
- [Tom] Spock!
(high-pitched droning)
- [Crow] Ah, Barbara
Streisand nails.
- [Tom] What is
your secret, man?
- That was close.
- [Joel] Hey come on,
she was just a rebound.
- You saved my life, mon ami.
We Frenchmen, we have a
weakness for pretty women.
- [Crow] Is that relevant?
- Yes, I should have known
that such a pretty creature
will not be at this early hour.
But I was robbed of all
thoughts, except one.
(goofy laughing)
- Why did you come here?
- [Tom] I am French, you know.
- I don't remember.
Wait, mon dieu.
- What is it?
- Branton.
- What about him?
- He's in that mill.
I'm sure of it, I saw his horse.
Sacre bleu.
- [Tom] Did I mention
that I am French?
- [Joel] Do we need a key?
- [Crow] No, just walk right in.
- [Tom] Hello, I am French.
- [Crow] Let's look at
the menu before we order.
- Sir Branton!
- [Dennis] Signoir Branton?
- Well, good morning gentlemen.
- [Tom] Two for smoking, then?
I am French you
know, very French.
- Is it good?
- [Joel] Sure, but is it safe?
- May we ask what
you're doing here?
- Someone has to do
the thinking for you.
As your commander,
I thought it wise
to spy out the countryside.
The upper floor of this mill
was the only vantage point.
- The last time you spied out
the land, Sir Anthony died.
- You can always turn
back, Sir Dennis.
- You have heard
my answer to that.
- As you will.
Shall we wake the
others and ride on?
- [Joel] Can't argue with
this guy, he's real smart.
- Gentlemen.
- [Crow] Ladies.
- [Tom] Age before beauty,
pearls before swine.
- [Crow] I know,
don't get me started.
- [Tom] Okay, pan right.
Pan right.
- [Joel] Keep panning.
- [Tom] Pan, pan, pan.
Pan pizza.
Personal pan.
(yelling)
- I almost had him, I tried.
I could have killed them
both, but that shield.
I couldn't face it.
- [Crow] You look like Worf.
- Yes, that shield.
- [Joel] Mark Shields, Brooke
Shields, Shields and Yarnell.
- Of course the boy has magic.
How else could he have
escaped three curses?
Magic
- [Tom] Courage!
- That foster mother Sybil
is working against me.
- His magic is strong, Lodac.
I know it.
How will you counter it?
Won't you need your ring?
- Not for Sybil's magic.
- [Joel] I can't look at you.
- When I get my ring...
- [Crow] I can do most anything!
- The princess will
be fed to my dragon.
All I have to do now is
to redouble my magic.
- [Tom] Is she on a spring?
- [Joel] Bobblehead.
- Was destroy that Frenchman!
You were too slow.
You need to be taught a lesson.
- No!
- Crawl, hag, crawl!
For five, six, ten hours.
Crawl until I need you again.
- [Crow] Help me, help me.
- [Joel] She's
finally the size two
she always wanted to be.
- Greetings, Sybil.
- [Tom] Ahh!
- Lodac.
- You're looking older.
- Thank you, Charlie Zan.
- What, a hundred years?
- I don't want to talk to you.
- But I want to talk to you.
- [Tom] About Amway.
- You've caused me
quite a lot of trouble.
- Lodac, if you've
touched a hair
on my boy's head,
I'll fight you.
- [Joel] Weird sexual tension.
- Not a chance.
You never had any really
talent for witchcraft.
- [Crow] You're a hack.
- Tenth-rate?
- You're quite helpless, Sybil.
In four days, the
princess Helene
will be fed to my dragon.
And your George will die
even sooner than that.
There's nothing you can do
except look in your stupid
mirror or magic pool.
And now I'll take care of that.
- Lodac, come back, come back!
- [Tom] Oh, now she'll
have to hang around
all day Tuesday waiting
for the cable guy.
- Mirror of magic, bring
me a vision of Lodac.
- [Crow] No.
- [Tom] Well, guess I'll just
have to read a good book then.
Let's see, Jurassic
Park, The Firm...
- [Joel] Red room, red room.
- Tenth-rate, am I?
Helpless, am I?
- [Tom] It's Estelle
Winwood's one-woman show.
- [Joel] Give 'em hell, Estelle.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] I'd go see that.
- So, I can't do
anything to help George.
- [Joel] I'm going
to get loaded.
- [Crow] Hey, knock it off!
- Lodac, you'll
be sorry for this.
- [Joel] Oh, there's an early
Krups machine right there.
- It's been a long time
since I've tried this one.
♪ Been a long time since
I've rocked and rolled ♪
- One, I'm sure
Where is the unicorn powder?
Oooh.
- [All] Oooh.
- [Crow] She should
not be left alone.
- [Tom] She's the type who
writes to Dear Abby, you know.
(instrumental theme music)
- [Crow] Hey keep
it down in there,
people work in the morning!
- I wonder what
Sybil's cooking up.
- [Joel] Trouble.
(goofy laughing)
She done it again.
(laughing)
(humming sitcom music)
- [Tom] Lucy, have you
been scheming again?
- What have you done, Sybil?
- I've finished poor George,
that's what I've done.
I've taken his magic
away from him completely.
- George has no more magic,
(Tom makes sad trombone notes)
- [Joel] We'll be back
with two separate views
of love, American-style.
- [Crow] Butch and Sundance,
the really early years.
- James, Dennis,
where are ya now?
- There are the tracks
of their horses.
- [Tom] Or the
tracks of my tears.
- I can't believe
they're ahead of us.
- [Crow] I can't
believe it's not butter.
- It's gettin'
hotter by the moment.
- [Joel] Why don't you take
off six or seven layers?
- What could I do?
They were up before daylight,
and belligerent at that.
Sir Dennis said that
he couldn't trust me
to spy out the land any longer.
- You could have wakened us.
- [Tom] Woken.
- They swore they'd be
back before daylight.
- Dennis, James!
- [Tom] Stella!
- They'll be burnt to
a crisp by this time.
- [Crow] By this time, my
lungs were burnt to a crisp.
- [Joel] Dreezil
drozil drozil drome,
time for these two to come home.
- [Tom] Help, Mr. Wizard.
- [Joel] Hey, it's Peter
Garrett from Midnight Oii
and his double.
- [All] Ugh.
- [Crow] Looks like their
jelly donuts blew up.
- Get back!
- [Tom] To the five and
dime, Jimmy Dean, Jimmy Dean!
- [Joel] The hills have eyes.
Kind of.
- Dennis!
- James!
- [Tom] Elaine!
- Will you be
looking at that man?
- [Tom] I'm Irish, you know.
- He's not even hot
and we're burning, why?
- [Tom] Aye, I'm Irish.
- Yes, why, Branton?
- That, gentlemen, is my secret.
- [Crow] It's strong enough for
a man, but made for a woman.
- [Tom] But wait,
what's your secret?
Come on, tell me, wait.
- [Crow] I can't hear
you, I'm not listening!
- [Tom] Come on, you gotta
tell us, what's your secret?
Come on, hey!
- [Crow] I can't hear you!
(humming gibberish)
(all imitating
train approaching)
- [Joel] We're not
going in there, buddy.
- The horses won't
go in the cave.
- [Joel] Oh, I'm
not goin' in there,
it's not part of
the union contract.
- [Tom] Just park it here.
Lock it up, there we go.
- [All] Surprise!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- [Tom] Oh.
- [George] Branton.
- [Joel] Echo.
Guys, this isn't funny.
- Where the devil is he?
- [Tom] Di-vil?
- [Joel] He's Irish.
- He's in here somewhere.
- [Branton] You mean
I was in here, George.
- Sir Branton!
- I'm sorry I have
to leave you know.
I've got a longstanding
appointment with
the princess Helene
and also with my partner Lodac.
- Partner!?
- Yes, his castle is
just over the hill.
Any last words for
either of them?
- [All] Help!
- I already have
escaped you, George.
- [Joel] Ladies and gentlemen,
the magic of David Copperfield.
♪ It's a brick house ♪
- [Crow] Okay,
where's Alan Funt?
- [Joel] We thought
it would be funny...
- We break out.
With Ascalon's help.
- Ascalon?
- [Crow] You
Ascalon, I'm bitter.
♪ Ascalon ♪
- Doors, walls, gates, anything.
(sword clanging)
(nervous laughing_
- [Tom] You see, the
batteries are kinda low.
It's lithium.
- Like your horse.
Perhaps Lodac's magic
is a bit stronger.
(sword clanging)
- [Joel] Please
wear safety goggles
If you're going
to do that, guys.
- You'll only be
dulling the blade.
- [Tom] The movie's
duller than that blade.
- There must be some
other way out, Patrick.
- [Crow] Well, I can
only conclude one thing.
We're gonna die!
(screaming)
- [Joel] You know,
I was just thinking,
a little wallpaper,
some carpeting,
this place could be
fixed up real nice.
- [Tom] I dub you Sir
Moron, come on dummy.
- [Joel] How come all
movies end in a cave?
- [Tom] To Kill a
Mockingbird didn't.
- [Joel] Well you're
right about that.
- [Crow] At Long
Last Love didn't
- [Joel] That's true.
- [Tom] To Have and
Have Not Anna Christie?
- [Joel] Three.
You're right, just
about all of 'em,
none of 'em ended in a cave.
- [Tom] What the, this place
is filled with breadsticks.
Hey, are we in
someone's epiglottis?
- [Crow] Oh, just a cheap
Bert I. Gordon special effect.
Nope, nothing happening
with the plot over here.
- [Tom] Nothing
over here either.
All clear.
- [Joel] It's Ho Chi Min.
- Patrick!
- [Crow] It's the New Monkees!
- [All] Guilty, guilty, guilty!
- [Joel] You know
what, I just realized
we're in The Ghost and Mr.
Chicken, let's get outta here!
(screaming)
- [Tom] Oh they're not dead,
they're just
metaphysically challenged.
- [Crow] The faces
of those he's wronged
are floating up at him!
- [Tom] Jimmy Smits.
[Joel] Hall's
vapor action, yeah.
(screaming)
- [Tom] So?
- [Joel] I am the god of
hellfire, and I bring you...
- [Tom] Yeah, he's battling
his own demons here.
- [Joel] Oh boy, this is
becoming the Green Ghost game.
- [Tom] Neat.
- [Crow] There's something
you don't see every day.
- [Tom] Pretty much.
Guy writhing in hell, soul
torn out from underneath him.
- [Patrick] Through the
walls, through the walls!
- [Tom] So I'll just leave then.
I guess.
- [Crow] Oh great, now
we're stuck in here.
[Tom] That was an interesting
scene, but one question.
What the heck just
happened here!?
- [Joel] Trippy.
- [Crow] I'll be here
if you need me, George.
- [Tom] He's dead, Jim.
- [Joel] See, you get to
pick out your own steak.
Watch this, I'll have that one.
- [Crow] Hmm, neat
stuff, but is it art?
- He's escaped again!
- Sir Patrick too.
- [Joel] And Toto too.
- Patrick is finished but Sir
George is riding this way.
- There was no way out
of that cave, Lodac.
Was it magic?
- [Tom] Or was it Memorex?
You decide.
- Not magic.
- Then how did George escape?
- I think, yes...
Something stronger than magic.
- [Joel] Double secret magic.
- [Lodac] The power
of Patrick's faith.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Fellas, I've got
something to say
and there's only
one way to do it,
so gimme center stage!
- Hey, be my guest,
it's all yours.
♪ As you guys I'm
sure remember ♪
♪ think it was maybe
last December ♪
♪ I fell, pell-mell,
for Kim Cattrall ♪
- Yeah, we remember.
Please don't remind us.
♪ But now I'm over that ♪
- Oh that's good.
♪ We had a little spat ♪
- In your dreams, buddy.
♪ I'm older, wiser and I know ♪
♪ that my true love
is really named ♪
♪ Estelle ♪
- [Tom] Winwood?
- [Crow] She's swell!
♪ She's cute ♪
♪ She's rooty-toot-toot ♪
♪ I bet she smells
like Juicy Fruit ♪
♪ She can really play a witch ♪
♪ She was even on Bewitched ♪
♪ And I'm bewildered
and bothered ♪
- Oh but Crow, hold
on a second, hold on.
- Thank you.
♪ Crow, you are my buddy ♪
♪ And maybe I'm a fuddy duddy ♪
♪ But step back please ♪
♪ And think about some stuff ♪
- like what?
♪ I'm sure that she seems nice ♪
♪ But I bet she's more
than twice your age ♪
♪ And with your love
it might not matter ♪
♪ But can she
control her bladder ♪
- Shut up!
- Tom, come on.
- Okay, okay, but Joel,
there's a whole other
set of issues here.
If I may, Crow, as a friend?
As a trusted adviser?
- Well...
- Okay.
Here's a quick list of people
much better looking than Estelle
- You're so shallow.
♪ Fred Biletnikoff,
Brandon Tartikoff,
Sid and Marty Krofft ♪
- Very funny.
♪ Fred Gwynne and
Anthony Quinn ♪
♪ And Rin Tin Tin
and Pearl Bailey ♪
♪ And Moms Mabley
and Mayor Daley ♪
♪ And Hank and Phoebe Snow ♪
- I'm not listening.
♪ Ethel Merman and Pee Wee
Herman and Strom Thurmond ♪
♪ and Vince Lombardi and
George and Jesus Jones. ♪
- I don't care, I don't care!
♪ Edith Head and Mister Ed ♪
♪ and Nostradamus
and Danny Thomas ♪
♪ and Leona and
Sherman Hemsley ♪
- Joel, make him stop!
- Tom, you're not
helping things at all.
Now, can you go and please
clip those coupons
like you promised?
- Uhhh, okay.
♪ Willy DeVille and
Agnes de Mille ♪
♪ and Cruella DeVille
and Roscoe Tanner and ♪
- Crow, listen.
Don't worry about it, friend.
Why don't you tell us more
about how you're feeling?
- Thank you.
♪ She's a vision ♪
♪ I got a new mission. ♪
♪ Somehow I got to meet her. ♪
♪ So she's older ♪
♪ two, three, four ♪
♪ She's got a great motor ♪
♪ There's nothing
that can beat her ♪
♪ Crow, you have my blessing. ♪
♪ And I feel like confessing ♪
♪ You're my little pal ♪
♪ Go on and give it a try. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
bewildered and bothered ♪
- Hey everybody, we'll be back
with more stuff here on MST3K.
(instrumental theme music)
Welcome to White Castle,
can I take your order?
- [Crow] Yeah, I'll have some
onion chips, some fries--
Hey!
- [Joel] Just kidding.
Move forward, friend.
(laughing)
- [Tom] I love that.
- He's coming.
- [Tom] Would you stop
looking into the fire,
for crying out loud?
- He's arriving at
the castle gate.
- [Joel] Hello?
- [Crow] We'll be
open in a minute, sir.
- - [Tom] The castle
has an open air
which gently and sweetly
recommends itself on the senses.
- [Crow] I can't believe
I paid eight bucks
and they don't even
have a tour guide.
- [Joel] Oh look, he's
a Swiss Army soldier.
- [Tom] Neat.
So is that a toothpick I see?
Knute Rockne, all-american!
- [Joel] Hoody-hoo,
hoody-hoo, hoody-hoo!
- [Crow] The wizard's not in.
- [Joel] Trick or
treat for UNICEF?
- [Tom] Uh, hi Mrs. Jones, I'm
here to pick up your daughter
and see if I can take her to--
(door closing)
♪ Walk right in,
sit right down ♪
♪ Daddy let your mind roll on ♪
- [Joel] Um, one, two,
uh three, uh, four,
three, four five six.
(cackling)
- [Tom] And then Johnny said,
"If you move your cat, lady!"
But you know, I kid all crows.
- [Crow] Hey, crows!
Hey, brothers, come back.
Mimes, I hate these guys.
- [Tom] Huzzah.
- Where is he going?
- [Joel] Scarborough Fair.
- No Lodac, I won't allow that.
- Don't worry,
it'll all work out
most satisfactory, I promise.
- He doesn't know the
way to her cell anyway.
- He doesn't have to.
The spell of the sixth curse
is already leading him on.
- [Tom] Here, pull my finger.
- [Joel] You know, I bet
people are always saying
to that guy, "Watch your
head, watch your head!"
(chuckling)
- [Tom] Poor guy.
- [Crow] Lawrence, would you
put that shield down please?
- [Tom] Oh, he's gotta have
a bathroom around
here somewhere.
I really gotta go.
- [Crow] Wow, a virgin!
- Helene!
- [Joel] No, like a virgin.
- [Crow] Virgin 2.0.
- Helene!
- George?
- [Joel] I've been
waiting all my life
for a guy named George.
- But you are George!
Or is this more
of Lodac's magic?
- I'm as real as you are.
- [Tom] Unfortunately.
- [Joel] Well, you'll do.
- How did you know me?
- Oh, I think I would
have known you anywhere.
Lodac has shown me visions
of you just to torture me.
Coming nearer and nearer.
- [Tom] Duh, girl pretty.
- But I'm here, and
we'll leave together.
- I'm too happy to even think.
- [Tom] No stretch for her.
- Just let me hold you.
- [Joel] Hey, you guys just met.
- - What happened
to Sir Branton?
- Rather ask what will happen
when I get him within
my sword's length.
- [Joel] Hey, that's dirty.
- He's somewhere
here in the castle.
- Let him go, what does
anything matter except us
and our freedom together?
- [Joel] You know, she's got
a real Barbara Eden quality.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- I'll see if the way is clear.
- [Crow] Later, later.
(panting)
- [Joel] You know, this is
a lot like Romeo and Juliet.
- [Crow] Except not good.
- [Tom] Pretty much.
Personally I think it's more
like a Ritz Brothers movie.
- [Crow] Except it's good.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] Okay, act natural.
We're vacationers from Japan.
- [Joel] 12 angry mimes.
- [Tom] It's the
Serendipity Singers!
- Welcome, Sir George.
- [Crow] To the
Renaissance Festival!
- I was beginning to think
you'd never get here.
You looking for this?
- [Tom] You just found it.
- My lady, it's time
for us to leave.
- Helene, no!
- But I want to, George.
- [Joel] He's a senior.
- Aren't you forgetting
something, Branton?
- [Crow] Oh, my purse.
- Oh, the ring.
- [Tom] Here you go, with
this ring I thee wed.
Can I go now?
- All right, take her.
- [Crow] Here, in front
of the circus people?
- Oh, I want her all right
And she wants me.
- Always and forever.
- Helene...
- What is this?
- [Joel] Chopped liver?
- [Crow] Yes, exactly.
- Helene!
- Did you really think I'd keep
my word once I had the ring?
- But I don't understand!
Where is Helene?
- Over here.
- She belongs to me,
we made a bargain.
- I don't bargain with
mortals, I destroy them!
ú- Monster!
- All right Branton, it's
time to take care of you!
- [Tom] Ba-boom!
- [Joel] Oh, he's been framed.
(laughing)
- Prepare her for the dragon.
- [Joel] No, no.
- Helene!
- [Tom] Meanwhile, on
the set of Golden Girls.
- I mustn't give up or
it's the end of him,
the end of them both.
- What will you do, Sybil?
- I must think.
Think, try to remember
the right recipe.
(Crow imitating chimp)
- Where did I go wrong?
- [Joel] Well, dyeing your
hair orange was a start.
- Witches of Hecate, blacker
than black, demons of shade--
- [Tom] I want my baby back.
- The next line, that's
the one I got wrong.
And it rhymes with rack.
- Flack, smack?
Snack?
- No, no, none of those.
I'll go to Lodac's castle,
that's what I'll do.
I'll give it some
thought on the way.
- Save him, Sybil.
- [Joel] It's a living.
- I'll try.
Well, here goes.
- [Crow] Sam, are
you conjuring again?
- [Joel] Come
back, you dummkopf.
- [Tom] Twin geeks.
- [Crow] Aye carumba.
- [Joel] It's equipped with
hot and cold running
Gary Lockwood.
- This is the real
Helene, I swear it.
- [Tom] And I'm the
real Inspector Hound.
- Go ahead, show me how a
pair of young mortals in love
bid farewell before they die.
(humming suggestive music)
- But a little late,
wouldn't you say?
- [Tom] I'm gonna have
to hose you two off
like a couple of
dogs, knock it off.
- I love you, Helene.
♪ I honestly love you ♪
- Come, helene.
Come!
- [Crow] Yech, she
rubbed his bronzer off.
- From the window, Sir George.
- [Joel] Um, and call room
service if you need anything.
Bye-bye.
- The feast, the feast!
Lodac will want a feast.
- [Tom] She's doing stand-up.
- You'll pick the wine.
The rest of you know
what you have to do.
- [All] Ahh!
- [Tom] I can't
get used to that.
♪ Little dudes in
a golden cage ♪
- [Joel] Um, my puzzler hurts.
- [Crow] Darby O'gill
and the Little People
will be back after this.
- [Tom] I just realized,
I'm Gary Lockwood.
- Helene!
(instrumental theme music)
- [Crow] Benjamin, I told
you not to go out with her.
- [Joel] Hey, her columns are
a lot more ornate than mine.
- [Crow] I wonder if I get
a continental breakfast.
- [Tom] Hey, Mr. Lockwood.
Mr. Lockwood.
We're here to help ya.
- [Joel] Let's go surfing
now, everybody's learning how.
Go scissor surfing with me.
- [Crow] I love
those little guys.
- [Tom] I thought
they cut this scene.
- [Crow] Like they
can't find him.
- [Tom] Oh look, it's Snap,
Crackle, Pop, Tony and...
- [Joel] Hi Gary, we're part
of this complete breakfast.
- [Crow] They must've gotten
laid off from Keebler.
- Hurry.
Please, quick, hurry!
- [Tom] Shave my armpits!
- [Joel] Keep your
shirt on, big guy.
Nothing's good enough for you!
- [Tom] Looks like a
Batman scene, doesn't it?
- Quick, cut the
ropes, my wrists!
(humming "Whistle
While You Work")
- [Crow] Come on, knock off
the elf crap and let me loose!
- [All] Oh my hands,
ow ow ow, sting, pain.
- My sword has lost its
magic but it's still a sword.
- - [Tom] Yeah right, whatever.
- [Crow] Hey, could
you help us out?
We're a little short.
(laughing)
Hi, when does the show start?
- [Joel] You are the show.
(roaring)
- [Joel] Is she doing her Fay
Wray or Jessica Lange in this?
- [Tom] Take your pick.
(roaring)
Enter the dragon.
- [Joel] Go on, let it out,
you're hurting
inside aren't you?
We could talk about this.
(horse neighing)
- [Crow] Bad Zippy, down!
Zippy, no, down!
- [Tom] Are we having fun yet?
- [Joel] Hey, self-serf.
- [Tom] Tonight's episode,
a double murder is
waiting for you.
- [Crow] Spot, no.
- Destroy him, it is my will!
- [Crow] Will schmill,
we got a job to do here.
- [Tom] I just had a little
Italian, I got heartburn.
I'm kidding of course.
- [Joel] The burning,
the itching, try Cruex.
- [Crow] Um, you won't
like me, I'm mock virgin.
I'm gamey, stringy and tough.
- [Tom] I don't care.
- [Joel] I didn't
know Estelle Winwood
qualified as a superhero.
- [Crow] Oh, yeah.
- [Tom] Well they
are good seats,
but I don't usually
like the balcony.
- [Joel] Hey, let's do
that thing where you put
the marshmallow on
your spear, it's fun.
- [Tom] Roast 'em,
tenderize 'em, down ya go.
- (roaring)
- [Crow] Aah, don't do that!
- Come to see the end of George?
- The ring.
- Yes, the ring.
- [Tom] Oh, he's Carnac and Ed.
(dragon roaring)
- Watch your boy!
- If only I could give
him back his magic.
Witches of Hecate,
blacker than black,
demons of shame and
flesh on the rack.
The next line.
- [Tom] Eenie meenie
chili beanie...
No, hernie hiney, no.
Oh damn.
- [Joel] Lighten up,
they're just puppets!
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Joel] Sorry.
- [Tom] Fire breathing's
good though, huh?
- [Crow] This is better
than the tanning bed.
- [Tom] Oops, ouch.
(screaming)
Not very nice.
- [Joel] Oh George, I gotta
get going, I'll see ya.
- [Tom] I'm okay, ooh.
- He's even lost
the power to attack.
- That's the word.
Witches of Hecate,
blacker than black.
- [Joel] I want my baby back.
- Give to my boy
the power to attack.
- [Tom] Uh, thanks Mom,
but I was already doin' it.
(roaring)
- [Crow] Darryl Dragon.
Hey, you're gonna poke an
eye out with that thing!
- [Tom] Sounds like
Godzilla all of a sudden.
- [Joel] Next week on
American Gladiators.
- [Crow] You know, if
this were a Japanese film,
the whole movie would revolve
around this dragon here?
- No!
- [Joel] The secret
compartment of the ring I fill
with a proton super-energy pill.
- It's my ring now.
- [Tom] She's right,
it's her ring now.
(growling)
- [Crow] Oh no, he snores.
- [Tom] I'm so sleepy I
can barely keep awake.
- [Joel] Ah, my braces.
Owie.
- [Crow] Well,
he's roadkill now.
- [Tom] Oh, the
other head died too.
How 'bout that.
- [Joel] Looks like
the George monster's
gonna score tonight,
that's for sure.
- [Crow] It's a magic sword
but it's also good
for simple jobs.
- They will still die!
- [Tom] Well eventually,
I suppose, but...
- - [Crow] Here, gimme
your gown, I gotta
wipe this blood up.
- Now I curse you with
all the damnation of hell!
Curse upon curse.
- [Joel] Oooh, we're scared.
- Defiant mortal, you
dare to challenge me.
Six curses could
not destroy you,
but now you must
face the seventh, me!
The invincible!
- [Joel] Oh go to bed, old man.
- Now will I grind you to dust!
Now all you vile
creatures of hell,
listen to me as I cast
the seventh curse!
- [Crow] Oh big deal,
you got an echo box.
So you went to Radio Shack.
I'm quaking.
- [Joel] The year of the cat,
in the morning of
the Bogart movie.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Dino, no boy!
(imitating barking)
Dino, no, stop!
- [Crow] Oh goodness
gracious, I'm dead.
(trumpet music)
- [Joel] Maynard Ferguson, live
at the Ashwaubenon
High School auditorium.
- [Tom] Mawwiage, twue love.
- [Crow] Now I'll kiss you.
- [Tom] No, that's
okay dad, please.
- [Joel] In a private
ceremony, they were married
by Grady from Sandford and Son.
- [Crow] Hey everyone,
it's Scooter and Skunk
and Chopper, he's nutty.
- [Tom] He's a dinger.
Oh, can't we do anything
without your friends?
- [All] Hi-keeba.
- [Crow] Ah, I owe 'em money.
Oh, Estelle.
- [Tom] Hey, my own mom just
flipped me off. How 'bout that?
- [Joel] Grady,
quit watchin' them
and get your butt over here.
(humming Sandford
and Son theme music)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Uh, you know Joel?
- Yes Tom?
- I just gotta say
that Bert I. Gordon
did quite a pretty
good job on that film
but one thing I'm confused about
is the whole concept
of the seven curses.
I didn't know you
could say curses on TV.
- Well it's not
that kind of curse.
To give you an example,
it's more like the curse
for people when
they performed on
Rick Dees' Into The Night
show, it's that kinda curse.
- Oh, got it.
You know, speaking
of seven curses,
despite what George Carlin said,
there are seven naughty
words you can say on TV.
- Oh sure, I know one.
Like hinder.
- Booger.
- Nimbus.
- Poopie.
- Dink.
- Caca.
- Booby.
- I think that's
seven right there.
- Wait a minute,
there's more than that.
There's underpants, ding-a-ling.
- Uh, stinkybutt, dickweed.
- Okay, okay,
that's plenty, okay.
- Uh, Joel, how about...
(whispering)
- Oh I don't think
you should, really.
- Just thought I'd check.
- Yeah, thanks for asking.
Anyway, I think it's
time to do a letter.
This is from Bill and
Tony Lorinson, okay,
and they said, 18 months ago,
oh, let's put that up
on still store, Cambot.
18 months ago we
moved from Ohio,
leaving our two children
in college there.
Having conversations
with our daughter Sue
was never a problem, she's
always had lots to talk about.
Isn't that like a teenage girl?
Anyway, however our son Bill...
- Bill has a problem.
- Bill is a sophomore
at Ohio State,
and really never believed
that your letters were true.
I'm kidding of course.
And having conversations
with him that produced
more than one or two-word
responses proved more difficult.
That has all changed
since we discovered MST3K
on a cable channel
here in Virginia
that is not available
in Columbus.
Knowing his bizarre sense
of humor is probably
genetic in origin, and
knowing how addicted he is
to our MST3K bi-weekly fixes,
we began taping your shows
regularly and
sending them to Bill.
The amazing results are
long detailed chats about
the latest tapes, and
comparing the parts
we found most hilarious.
So kudos to guys and
Gypsy for finding a way
for parents and kids to connect.
When people ask us
how we manage to stay
in such close touch with
Bill and his generation
because they too want
to enjoy that kind of
meaningful relationship
with their kids,
we simply tell them, keep
circulating the tapes.
Thanks.
What do you think, sirs?
- Oh, is the great Joel Robinson
bridging the
generation gap again?
Aaah, push the button, Frank.
- Doctor, I don't feel too good.
I think that biohazard
whatever stuff
is having an effect on me.
- Really?
You look great.
- I do?
- Yeah, yeah, let's
go get a pizza.
I'll bring the mad
scientist-mobile around.
- Oh, I don't think I
could hold a pizza down.
- Well, maybe we'll
get you some soup.
(groaning)
(somber instrumental music)